Hey Brandon, want to build a robot?
やあ ブランドン ロボットは作りたいですか?
Sure, sounds good. Looks like you've got some hardware here. What's left to do?
もちろんです いいですねここにハードウェアがあるようですほかにやるべきことがありますか?
Yeah. All we need to do now is write device drivers for all our sensors and actuators,
そうです今やらなければならないのは すべてのセンサーとアクチュエーター用のデバイス ドライバーを書き
develop a communications framework that can support four different protocols,
4 つの異なるプロトコルをサポートできる通信フレームワークを介し
write algorithms to do perception,
知覚 ナビゲーション モーション プラニングを行うための
navigation and motion planning.
アルゴリズムを書きます
Yeah. And then after that,
はいその後
we can implement a mechanism to log our data,
データを記録するメカニズムを実装することができ
write our control algorithms,
制御アルゴリズムを書き
oh, and don't forget error handling.
エラー処理を忘れないでください
Awesome. Let's get started.
素晴らしいそれでは始めましょう
So, how's it going guys?
調子はどうですか
Great.
書けましたか?
Yeah, we got the lights to turn on.
ライトの電源を入れました
Building a robot used to be a long and cumbersome process.
ロボットの製造は 以前は長くて面倒な作業でした
All the components had to essentially be built from scratch.
すべてのコンポーネントは本質的にゼロから構築されなければなりませんでした
In this lesson, we'll be giving you an introduction to robot operating system or ROS,
このレッスンでは ロボットの開発を大幅に簡素化するソフトウェア フレームワークである ロボット オペレーティング システム
which is a software framework that greatly simplifies robot development.
（ROS）について紹介します
There are many advantages to developing robots with ROS.
ROS を使ってロボットを開発することには多くの利点があります
But before we dive deep,
掘り下げる前に
I think we should explain what ROS actually is.
ROS が実際に何であるかを説明するべきだと思います
Indeed, ROS is an open source software framework for robotics development.
実際 ROS はロボット開発のためのオープンソース ソフトウェア フレームワークです
To help you get a better understanding of what ROS is,
ROS とは何かをよりよく理解するために
let's illustrate some of its components and features.
コンポーネントと機能のいくつかを説明しましょう
ROS is not an operating system in the typical sense,
ROS は典型的な意味ではオペレーティング システムではありません
but like an OS, it provides a means of talking
しかし OS のように
to hardware without writing your own device drivers.
デバイス ドライバーを書かずにハードウェアに話す手段を提供します
It also provides a way for different processes
また 異なるプロセス
to communicate with one another via message passing.
がメッセージ パッシングを介して互いに通信する方法を提供します
Lastly, ROS features a sleek build and
最後に ROS は洗練されたビルドと
package management system allowing you to develop and deploy software with ease.
パッケージ管理システムを特徴としており 簡単にソフトウェアを開発して展開することができます
ROS also has tools for visualization, simulation and analysis,
ROS には ビジュアライゼーション シミュレーション 分析のためのツール
as well as extensive community support and
広範なコミュニティサポート
an interface to numerous powerful software libraries.
多数の強力なソフトウェア ライブラリへのインターフェースがあります
Before diving deeper into all this,
このことについて深く考える前に
let's take a brief tour of the history of ROS.
ROS の歴史について考えてみましょう